Guide to the Matt Phillips Sketchbooks, 1962-2008 M1046
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- [Sketchbook], 1999 May 8; Sketchbook No. 118; 1 v.: pencil and watercolor, 10.5x15.5. Leaves nearly filled. (Box 9, Volume 121)
- [Sketchbook], 1999 May 19; 1 v.: pencil and watercolor, 15.5x15.5. Leaves half filled. (Box 9, Volume 122)
- [Sketchbook] Stanford University sketch bk.: Stanford University begun 12/23/99, finished 5/6/00. Matt Phillips, 1999-2000; 1 v.: pencil and watercolor, 20.5x15.5. Leaves filled. (Box 10, Volume 123)
- [Sketchbook] Paris, Beaches, Family, 1965-66-67: 1965, 1966, 1967 Phillips w/colors crayons, 1965 - 1969; 45 leaves: pencil, crayon, water color, 27 x 21. Leaves filled. (Box 10, Volume 124)
- [Sketchbook] 1981-85: fall, 1981; spring, 1983; [s.s.] 1993-1994, 1981 - 1985; 80 leaves used; some on both sides & multiple sketches leaves: pencil, some pen, 22 x 28. (Box 10, Volume 125)
- [Sketchbook] China, 17 May 2000 (Box 10, Volume 126)
- [Sketchbook] Japan, 5/7/2001 - 5/22/2001 (Box 10, Volume 127)
- [Sketchbook] San Francisco - Philadelphia, 4/18/2002; New York, London, Paris, 5/14/2002 (Box 10, Volume 128)
- [Sketchbook] Marrakech 5/8/2002 (Box 10, Volume 129)
- [Sketchbook] Montana, 2000 August-October (Box 10, Volume 130)
- [Sketchbook] Ranunculas and fruits, January 2003 (Box 11, Volume 131)
- [Sketchbook] Nudes, 21 January 2001 - 3 May 2003 (Box 11, Volume 132)
- [Sketchbook] New york, 30 March - 6 April 2000; Chicago, 6 April - 9 April 2000; New York 2 January - 9 January 2002. (Box 11, Volume 133)
- [Sketchbook] Montana 8/13/01 - 8/28/03 (Box 11, Volume 134)
- Vietnam & Cambodia, undated (Box 11, Volume 135)
- [Sketchbook] Studies for Song of Solomon 5/26/04 (Box 11, Volume 136)
- [Sketchbook] Beaches 1999-2000 (Box 12, Volume 137)
- [Sketchbook] Montana 2002 (Box 12, Volume 138)
- [Sketchbook] Montana 2007 (Box 12, Volume 139)
- [Sketchbook] New York City 1/14/2007 - 1/15-2007 (Box 12, Volume 140)
- [Sketchbook] 4/21/2008 (Box 12, Volume 141)